# **ELJAN BADALOV**

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Baku, Azerbaijan • +994505109720 • elcanbadalov06@gmail.com

### **SUMMARY**

I am a Frontend Developer candidate and I am focused on constantly improving myself. I gained experience in the field of web development by developing my own projects. I have a deep understanding of user interface design, usability and performance optimization.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Volunteer, Barda Asan Service Center

Sep 2023 - Nov 2023

We learned and taught new things for 2 months with a great team

# Volunteer, Karabakh Regional DOST Center

Sep 2023 - Nov 2023

 We learned and taught new things for 3 months with a great team, including DOST Volunteering

## **EDUCATION**

Tourism secondary qualification, Tourism and its organization

Sep 2020 - Jun 2023

Mingachevir Tourism College

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

# Frontend (JavaScript) Development

Jan 2023 - Oct 2023

TechAcademy

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS
- · Sass, Scss
- Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS
- Javascript
- React JS
- Redux Toolkit
- REST API
- Responsive Design

# **LANGUAGE**

- Azerbaijan Native
- Turkish Fluent
- English Basic
- Russian Conversational